{
    "subject": "resource/E._M._S._Namboodiripad",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Perintalmanna",
    "human_readable": "E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Perintalmanna.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9547414779663086,
            "question": "Name the city where E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9358116388320923,
            "question": "Where was E.M.S. Namboodiripad born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9351707696914673,
            "question": "When was E.M.S. Namboodiripad born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9095851182937622,
            "question": "In what country was E.M.S. Namboodiripad born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856888175010681,
            "question": "What is E.M.S. Namboodiripad known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.664449155330658,
            "question": "Was E.M.S. Namboodiripad a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5793139934539795,
            "question": "What was E.M.S. Namboodiripad's role in Indian politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5782431960105896,
            "question": "What were some of E.M.S. Namboodiripad's major achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5413523316383362,
            "question": "What political party was E.M.S. Namboodiripad associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4366456866264343,
            "question": "Did E.M.S. Namboodiripad hold any important government positions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Perintalmanna.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6787_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political party was E.M.S. Namboodiripad associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6787_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of E.M.S. Namboodiripad's major achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6787_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was E.M.S. Namboodiripad's role in Indian politics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6787_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6787_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate whether the statement about E.M.S. Namboodiripad's birthplace is correct.\n\nHere is the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention Perinthalmanna (or a variant of it) as the birthplace of E.M.S. Namboodiripad, or specifically refer to Perintalmanna taluk, which suggests that the statement about his birthplace is correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that E. M. S. Namboodiripad was born on June 13, 1909, in Perinthalmanna, Malabar district (now part of Kerala, India). This information supports the statement that E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Perintalmanna."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}